Guide to the Irene Peslikis Papers, 1957-2002 and undated RL.01018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Irene Peslikis papers
1957-2002 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Peslikis, Irene
RL.01018
27 Linear Feet
Feminist artist, activist, and educator Irene Peslikis (1943-2002) was born in New York, New York, and raised in different locations in Queens, New York. She was instrumental in a number of influential feminist and feminist art groups, including the New York Feminist Art Institute, the journal Women & Art (co-founded with Pat Mainardi), and the group Redstockings. The Irene Peslikis Papers span the years 1957-2002 and document Peslikis's life as a feminist artist, activist, and educator. The collection is organized into nine series: Feminist Activism, Correspondence, Writings, Personal Files, Subject Files, Education, Art, Printed Material, and Audiovisual Material. Materials in this collection include correspondence, essays, personal journals, exhibit files, artwork in a number of media, personal files, her student files, teaching files, clippings, photographs, journals, pamphlets, and audiocassettes. Frequent and/or notable correspondents include her immediate family: her mother, father, and brother, Michael; and friends Ursula Karau, Alix Kates Shulman, Rosalyn Baxandall, Robin Morgan, Carol Hanisch, Lucinda (Cindy) Cisler, Lucia Vernarelli, Pat Mainardi, Judy Chicago, and Shulamith (Shulie) Firestone.
20,250 Items
Access Restrictions
The contents of Box 20 are closed until 2099. With that exception, the collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Irene Peslikis Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in 2003.
Biographical Note
Feminist artist, activist, and educator Irene Peslikis was born 7 October 1943 in New York, New York. Upon completing high school in 1962, she began studies in art at Pratt Institute. In 1963, Peslikis, along with others, broke away from Pratt and co-founded the New York Studio School for Drawing, Painting, and Sculpture. She was a founding member of the feminist theoretical and consciousness raising group Redstockings, authored Resistances to Consciousness, a paper on understanding consciousness raising, and was one of the organizers of and participants in the Redstockings Speak Out on Abortion at Washington Square Methodist Church in New York City. Peslikis founded the journal Women & Art with another feminist artist, Pat Manairdi, in the early 1970s, and in 1973 graduated from Queens College.
The first Women and Art course on a college campus was taught by Peslikis at the State University of New York at Old Westbury, and she was a founder of the New York Feminist Art Institute. From the 1970s through 1980s, Peslikis taught at a number of post-secondary institutions, including the City College of New York, the College of Staten Island, the College of New Rochelle, and Ramapo College. She taught courses such as Painting, Drawing, Visual Arts Orientation, Introduction to Art Making, Women and Art Studio Workshop, and Contemporary Perspectives on Art. Peslikis had a number of solo art exhibitions, and participated in a larger number of group exhibitions. In 1983, she earned an MFA from the City College of New York. Peslikis died on 28 November 2002 at the age of 59.
Collection Overview
The Irene Peslikis Papers span the years 1957-2002 and document Peslikis's life as a feminist artist, activist, and educator. The collection is organized into nine series: Feminist Activism, Correspondence, Writings, Personal Files, Subject Files, Education, Art, Printed Material, and Audiovisual Material.
The Feminist Activism Series is composed of materials from three key venues for Peslikis's feminist activist work: the New York Feminist Art Institute, the journal Women & Art, and the group Redstockings. This series includes organizational records, related correspondence and articles, exhibition announcements, and grant proposals.
The Correspondence Series contains letters, postcards, and cards received by Peslikis from family and friends. Frequent and/or notable correspondents include her immediate family: her mother, father, and brother, Michael; and friends Ursula Karau, Alix Kates Shulman, Rosalyn Baxandall, Robin Morgan, Carol Hanisch, Lucinda (Cindy) Cisler, Lucia Vernarelli, Pat Mainardi, Judy Chicago, and Shulamith (Shulie) Firestone. A smaller amount of outgoing letters is also included. Correspondence depicts Peslikis's work as an activist and as an artist, as well as her financial and medical difficulties.
Materials in the Writings Series include manuscripts, notes, notebooks, and journals kept by Peslikis. The Manuscripts subseries includes writings by people other than Peslikis which directly impacted her work, as well as drafts and outlines of Peslikis's publications. Notes, notebooks, and journals were all penned by Peslikis. Notebooks are primarily personal journals kept by Peslikis from her teenage years through the early 1980s and again from the early 1990s until the end of her life.
The Personal Files Series depicts the numerous financial, legal, and medical issues confronted by Peslikis over three decades. Peslikis received assistance in the form of Supplemental Security Income (SSI), food stamps, and subsidized housing for artists (at Westbeth Artist Housing), each of which required meticulous documentation in order to retain. A portion of this series is closed until 2099.
The Subject Files Series consists primarily of clippings and notes retained by Peslikis on a number of women- and feminism-related subjects, as well as on art, astrology, United States foreign policy, and Greek politics.
The Education Series is composed of files documenting Peslikis as a student, an instructor, and an instructor in search of employment.
Items in the Art Series include artwork by Peslikis, duplications of her artwork, sketchbooks, and files related to her exhibits, including flyers, reviews, and catalogs.
The Printed Material Series comprises periodicals, pamphlets, and printed essays. Subjects represented include feminism, Marxism, and art.
The Audiovisual Material Series consists of audiocassettes and super 8 film documenting discussions, meetings, and other events. Items are labeled with original descriptions provided by Peslikis. Also included is a VHS tape of a memorial service for Peslikis.
Related Material
Women's and LGBT Movements Periodicals Collection
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
Art -- Study and teaching -- New York (State) -- New York; Art, American -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th century; Feminism and art; Feminism and art -- New York (State) -- New York; Feminism -- Study and teaching -- United States; Feminism -- United States; Multimedia (Art); Feminists -- United States -- Correspondence; Feminists -- United States; Feminists -- United States -- Political activity; Women artists -- United States -- Correspondence; Women artists; Cisler, Lucinda; Baxandall, Rosalyn Fraad; Mainardi, Patricia; Hanish, Carol; Firestone, Shulamith; Feminist Art Institute; Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture; Redstockings, Inc.; Peslikis, Irene; Vernarelli, Lucia; Shulman, Alix Kates; Chicago, Judy, 1939-; Morgan, Robin, 1941-
- Feminist Activism, 1965-2001 and undated, 5 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Peslikis was an integral element of a number of feminist efforts emerging from the second wave of feminism in the United States, including the New York Feminist Art Institute, the journal Women & Art, and the group Redstockings. Materials related to each organization are included in this series.
  - Feminist Art Institute, 1976-1982 and undated
    The New York Feminist Art Institute, of which Peslikis was a founding member, began in 1979 and offered a radical feminist art education for women. In 1981 Peslikis was voted off the Institute's board of directors, prompting the resignation of others. This stemmed from a disagreement about racial intergration in the Institute. Includes workshop and course announcements, related correspondence and articles, grant proposals, and letters of resignation from board members due to the controversy over the organization's racial politics. Arrangement is chronological.
    - Walton, Joanna, Anglo-American workshop, 1976 Mar.-Apr. (Box 1)
    - Pauley, Sylvia Nelson, Spring 1977-1978 (Box 1)
      [Note: Includes slides of her work.]
    - Notes, 1977 Nov.- 1978 May (Box 1)
    - Newspaper articles, 1977 Dec.-1979 July (Box 1)
    - Mailing lists, arts letters, and policies, 1977 Dec.-Summer 1979 (Box 1)
    - Course notes, procedures, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1978 Feb.-Dec. (Box 1)
    - Meeting notes, reports, and minutes, 1978 Mar.-Dec. (Box 1)
    - Proposals, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Grants, collage contributions, and other fundraising ideas, 1978 June-1979 May (Box 1)
    - Kurland, Roberta, dissertation seminar, Autumn 1978-1979 Jan. (Box 1)
    - Curriculum vitae and extra information on instructors, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Expenses, paid and unpaid, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Notes, curriculum analysis, 1979 Jan.-Mar. (Box 1)
    - Raffle benefit, fundraising, 1979 Jan.-Mar. (Box 1)
    - Mailing list information, 1979 Mar. (Box 1)
    - Fall preparation, printer's prices, 1979 Mar.-Aug. (Box 1)
    - Course descriptions, Summer 1979 (Box 1)
    - Forms, Summer 1979 (Box 1)
    - Original copy of schedule, flyer, and press release, Summer 1979 (Box 1)
    - Press release and programs, Summer 1979 (Box 1)
    - Workshop descriptions, Summer 1979 (Box 1)
    - Notes, course descriptions, 1979 May-July (Box 2)
    - Appointments, notes, 1979 June (Box 2)
    - Events, curriculum vitae, 1979 June-July (Box 2)
    - Notes, 1979 June-July (Box 2)
    - Summer program, preliminary proposal and objectives, 1979 June-July (Box 2)
    - Board meeting: original goals, summer program, progress report, 1979 July 18 (Box 2)
    - Meetings, 1979 July-Aug. notes (Box 2)
    - Brochures, flyers, Autumn 1979 (Box 2)
    - Workshop descriptions, Autumn 1979 (Box 2)
    - Notes, 1979 Sept. (Box 2)
    - Simone de Beauvoir conference papers, mailing list, and correspondence, 1979 Sept. 27-29 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors, notes, 1979 Oct. (Box 2)
    - Notes, correspondence, curriculum vitae, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
    - Proposal and projected first year budget, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
    - Commercial space availability, 1979-1980 Oct. (Box 2)
    - Proposals and budgets, 1979 Feb.-Spring 1980 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1979 July-1980 Mar. (Box 2)
    - Official documents, bylaws, and meeting minutes, 1979-1981 (Box 2)
    - Workshops and catalog, Summer 1979-1981 (Box 3)
    - Events, 1979 Nov.-1981 Apr. (Box 3)
    - Art Association presentation notes, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Personal notes, 1980 Mar.-Oct. (Box 3)
    - Attempts at community meetings, 1980 May 2 (Box 3)
    - Ford Foundation: correspondence, budgets, letters of recommendation, and notes, 1980 July-Dec. (Box 3)
    - Rules and regulations for raffle, 1980 Oct.-Dec. (Box 3)
    - Notes, minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
    - Political issues and aesthetics, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
    - Sexism/racism workshop, 1981 Jan. (Box 3)
    - Transformations exhibit, 1981 Mar. (Box 3)
    - Political consciousness/political action weekend, 1981 Apr. (Box 3)
    - Letters of resignation, Race and Politics at the N.Y.F.A.I., 1981 June-July (Box 3)
    - Catalog, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - Budget, proof, memo, undated (Box 3)
    - Notes, undated (Box 3)
    - Publicity information, inexpensive printing, undated (Box 3)
  - Women & Art, 1965-1977 and undated
    Feminist journal co-founded with Patricia Mainardi. Includes press releases, article submissions, exhibition announcements, and correspondence regarding the organization's liberal/Marxist split. Arrangement is chronological.
    - Articles, 1965-1972 (Box 3)
    - Notes on reductive art and art group agenda, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Articles and conference announcements, 1970 Mar.-1973 May (Box 3)
    - Manifestos of women artists, 1970 Mar.-1972 Mar. (Box 3)
    - New articles, 1970 Nov.-1971 Oct. (Box 3)
    - Notes on aesthetics, society, and criticism, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Articles and exhibition announcements, 1971 Apr.-July (Box 4)
    - Redstocking artists and fundraising for feminist gallery, 1971 May (Box 4)
    - Financial and administrative papers, 1971 May-1973 May, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Redstocking artists of the Woman Artists Group, 1971 June-Aug. (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 1971 Nov.-1972 Mar. (Box 4)
    - Female sexuality and censorship, 1972 (Box 4)
    - Egbert, Donald, The Idea of the Avante Gardein Art and Politics, 1972 Mar. (Box 4)
    - Liberal/Marxist split, 1972 Mar.-Apr. (Box 4)
    - Newsletters, 1971 Autumn-Winter (Box 4)
    - Proposal notes, 1971 May-1979 Aug. (Box 4)
    - Magazine contributions and art exhibition, Two Nations, Six Artists, 1972 Mar.-1974 Feb. (Box 4)
      [Note: Includes photographs and pen and ink drawings.]
    - Supplement, Summer/Autumn 1972 (Box 4)
    - Articles, 1973 (Box 4)
    - Ideas and correspondence, 1973 (Box 4)
    - Submissions, Spring 1973 (Box 4)
    - A Group Project, notes, 1974 Nov.-Dec. (Box 4)
    - Articles 1974-1975 May (Box 4)
    - Women & Art collective exhibit, 1975 Apr. (Box 4)
    - Women & Art exhibition, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Articles and events, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Women & Art workshop of American Studies, third annual exhibit, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Newsletter, articles, and catalog, 1977 Feb.-June (Box 5)
    - Bibliography and resource list, 1977 Apr. (Box 5)
    - Articles, undated (Box 5)
    - Lecture notes, Lehman College, undated (Box 5)
    - Notes regarding supplement on Marxist aesthetics, undated (Box 5)
  - Redstockings, 1968-2001 and undated
    A feminist theoretical and consciousness-raising group in New York City, which Peslikis co-founded. Includes articles on radical feminist politics and draft of the Redstockings Manifesto. Arrangement is chronological.
    - Consciousness-raising and Intuition, 1968 Nov. (Box 5)
    - Consciousness-raising, session outline, 1968 (Box 5)
    - What Can Be Learned?: A Critique of the Miss America Protest and Defining Reality, 1968 Nov. (Box 5)
    - Consciousness-raising, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Whatever Happened to Women?, The Politics of Free Love, and Consumerism and Women, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Resistance to Consciousness, 1969 June 27 (Box 5)
    - Testimonies: how marriage oppresses single women, 1969 Aug. (Box 5)
    - A Woman Scientist Speaks, 1969 Nov. 20 (Box 5)
    - Manifesto and notes, 1970 Mar. (Box 5)
    - Workshop on class, 1970 Apr.-May (Box 5)
    - Steinem, Gloria, press release, 1975 May 9 (Box 5)
    - Course description: Women Thinking About Themselves, Autumn 1978 (Box 5)
    - Abortion forum, 1989 Mar. 3 (Box 5)
    - Veteran feminists and women's liberation, 1999-2001 (Box 5)
    - Consciousness-raising evaluation event, 2000 Dec. 10 (Box 5)
    - Women's Liberation & National Health Care: Confronting the Myth of the Nation, 2001 Dec. 19 (Box 5)
    - Brainwashing and Women: The Psychological Attack, and False Consciousness, undated (Box 5)
    - Redstockings Manifesto, principles and letter, undated (Box 5)
- Correspondence, 1958-2002 and undated, 3 boxes
  Contains letters, postcards, and cards received by Peslikis from family and friends. Frequent and/or notable correspondents include her immediate family: her mother, father, and brother, Michael; and friends Ursula Karau, Alix Kates Shulman, Rosalyn Baxandall, Robin Morgan, Carol Hanisch, Lucinda (Cindy) Cisler, Lucia Vernarelli, Pat Mainardi, Judy Chicago, and Shulamith (Shulie) Firestone. A smaller amount of outgoing letters is also included. Correspondence depicts Peslikis's work as an activist and as an artist, as well as her financial and medical difficulties. Arrangement is chronological.
  - 1958 (Box 6)
  - 1960 June-1969 Oct. and undated (Box 6)
  - 1961 July-Sept. (Box 6)
  - 1962 Feb.-July (Box 6)
  - 1963 Sept. 10 (Box 6)
  - 1964 Feb.-Mar. (Box 6)
  - 1967 Mar. 3 (Box 6)
  - 1969 June-Aug. (Box 6)
  - circa 1970 (Box 6)
  - 1970 Mar.-June (Box 6)
  - 1971 Feb.-Dec. (Box 6)
  - 1972 (Box 6)
  - 1973 (Box 6)
  - 1974 Mar.-Sept. (Box 6)
  - 1975 May-Aug. (Box 6)
  - 1976 May-Oct. (Box 6)
  - 1977 (Box 6)
  - 1978 (Box 6)
  - 1978-1997 (Box 6)
  - 1979, 2 folders (Box 6A)
  - 1980 (Box 6A)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 7)
  - 1981 (Box 7)
  - 1981-1982 (Box 7)
  - 1982 (Box 7)
  - 1983 Feb.-Aug. (Box 7)
  - 1984 Feb. 25 (Box 7)
  - 1985 (Box 7)
  - 1986 (Box 7)
  - 1987 (Box 7)
  - 1988 Jan.-Mar. (Box 7)
  - 1989 Oct.-Nov. (Box 7)
  - 1990 July (Box 7)
  - 1990-1993 (Box 7)
  - 1990-1994 (Box 7)
  - 1991 (Box 7)
  - 1992 Jan.-Apr. (Box 7)
  - 1993 (Box 7)
  - 1994 (Box 7)
  - 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - 1997 (Box 8)
  - 1998, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - 1999 (Box 8)
  - 2000 (Box 8)
  - 2001-2002 (Box 8)
  - 2002 (Box 8)
  - undated, 3 folders (Box 8)
- Writings, 1960-2002 and undated, 8 boxes
  Contains manuscripts, notes, notebooks, and journals kept by Peslikis. The Manuscripts subseries includes writings by people other than Peslikis which directly impacted her work, as well as drafts and outlines of Peslikis's publications. Notes, notebooks, and journals were all penned by Peslikis.
  - Manuscripts, 1963-1994 and undated
    Includes early drafts, outlines, and related notes of Peslikis's publications as well as the creative and scholarly works of her associates and influences. Files are arranged alphabetically.
    - Anonymous, Encyclopedia Britannica submission on Crime and Punishment, undated (Box 9)
    - Anonymous, The Fire Last Time, undated (Box 9)
    - Berl, Christine, essay on the function of socialist art, notes, 1971 Jan. 3 (Box 9)
    - Chatwood, Kathleen, Art Under Capitalism, 1979 Feb. (Box 9)
    - De Beauvoir, Simone, The Question of Fidelity, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Dodge, Natt N., Poisonous Dwellers of the Desert, undated (Box 9)
    - Forer, Anne, Dedicated to Irene, Easter, Stories and Letters, Philosophy, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Forer, Anne, A Pink Cloud, A Spritual Struggle, and untitled story, 1989-1991 (Box 9)
    - Giardina, Carol Ann, A Critical Analysis of Marxist Theory and Practice on the Woman Question, 1970 June (Box 9)
    - Guerrier, Dexter, untitled play, 1980 Nov.-Dec. (Box 9)
    - Jarratt, Kent, My Brother's Friend and Irene's Story, undated (Box 9)
    - Jarratt, Kent, Noho Gallery article in honor of Peslikis's photo-collage exhibit, undated (Box 9)
    - Jarratt, Kent, Sunbathing and untitled poems, undated (Box 9)
    - Jarratt, Kent, This Saturday, The Decay of Stone, Tarantella, undated (Box 9)
    - Peslikis, essays on Marxism and modern art, 1969-1980, 7 folders (Box 9)
    - Peslikis
      - Random House permission release form for Women in Revolt, 1970 (Box 9)
      - Unfinished article and newspaper clippings, 1971 Sept.-1972 Jan. (Box 9)
      - Untitled speech, 1977 Mar. 16 (Box 9)
      - Heresies, introduction and outline, 1978 Dec.-1979 Mar. (Box 9)
      - Notes for Heresies, 1979 Jan. (Box 9)
      - Notes for Heresies and Reviewing my past thoughts, undated (Box 10)
      - et al., Men Have Died from Time to Time and Worms Have Eaten Them, But Not for Love: The Woman Artist and the Myth of Romantic Love, 1979 July 1 (Box 10)
      - Colette's Independent Study of A.H., Drawn from the Lifetime of Her Friend, and notes, 1979-1983 (Box 10)
      - Untitled fragments on the avant-garde, 1982 Mar.-1982 May (Box 10)
      - Untitled poem, circa 1982 Mar. 17 (Box 10)
      - Presentation on the context, form, and content of art, preliminary draft and notes, 1982 May 13 (Box 10)
      - Feminist Memoir Project, prospectus and notes, 1994 (Box 10)
      - Cooper/Grey cubist aesthetics, paper and notes, undated (Box 10)
      - Cooper/Grey paper, preliminary drafts, and notes on Simone de Beauvoir and Marxism, undated (Box 10)
      - Inevitable Truths, preliminary draft, undated (Box 10)
      - Resistance to Consciousness, prelimary drafts and notes, undated (Box 10)
      - Toward an Understanding of Marxist Theory on Art, undated (Box 10)
    - Peslikis, John, The Uncharted Voyage and other writings, 1966 Dec.-1993 Nov., 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Poussaint, Alvin F., The Stresses of the White Female Worker in the Civil Rights Movement in the South, 1966 May 13 (Box 10)
    - Rakow, Raymond W., Pro-Choice vs. Pro-Abortion: An Important Difference, Psychoanalysis and Psychosomatic Medicine, Sexual Freedom and Oppressive Ideology, Sex, Politics, and Psychology, 1982-1989 (Box 10)
    - Sheehy, Gail, Bachelor Mothers, undated (Box 10)
    - Sherman, Susan, untitled, undated (Box 10)
    - Shulman, Alix Kates, untitled paper, undated (Box 10)
    - Smith, Christine, Klimt's Image of Women, undated (Box 10)
    - Wahous, Jane, 1963-1967 Oct. (Box 10)
    - Winters, Laurence E., The Problematic of Contemporary Art: Impasse or Opening, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Zalamea, Pilar, Friend, undated (Box 10)
  - Notes, 1969-2002 and undated
    Includes Peslikis's outlines and research notes for her articles and activism, as well as personal reflections on these topics. Arrangement is chronological.
    - Speech notes on abortion and feminist history, 1969-1979 Mar. (Box 11)
    - Dialectical materialism, 1971-1989 (Box 11)
    - Some thoughts on Simone de Beauvoir, woman and history, 1971 Apr. (Box 11)
    - 1977 Aug.-1994 Aug. (Box 11)
    - Conference notes, 1978 Jan. (Box 11)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 11)
    - Expenses regarding WBAI program, 1978 Apr.-1979 Mar. (Box 11)
    - Art history and anthropology, 1979 Jan.-March, 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Dictaphone messages, 1983-1992, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Marriage, 1994-2002, 6 folders (Box 11)
    - Biological determinism, teaching, and Women's Movement, 1998-2000 (Box 11)
    - Foreign policy, historical chronology, 2000 Mar.-Apr. (Box 11)
    - Bibliographic information, undated (Box 11)
    - Contacts, undated, 3 folders (Box 12)
    - Lecture notes on Mary Cassatt, undated (Box 12)
    - Marxism and bourgeois radicalism, undated (Box 12)
    - Scrapbooking material, undated (Box 12)
    - Stop Smoking Guide and contacts, undated (Box 12)
    - Women's Movement, undated (Box 12)
  - Notebooks and Journals, 1960-1984, 1992-2002 and undated
    Consists primarily of personal journals kept by Peslikis from her teenage years through the early 1980s and again from the early 1990s until the end of her life. Arrangement is chronological.
    - 1960-1970 (Box 12)
    - Typed transcriptions of journal entries, 1960-1973 (Box 12)
    - 1961 (Box 12)
    - 1962 Nov.-1973 May (Box 12)
    - Loose leaf journal entries, 1963 Mar.-1996 Aug. (Box 12)
    - 1967 (Box 12)
    - 1968 (Box 12)
    - 1968 Mar.-1969 Dec. (Box 13)
    - 1968 Sept. (Box 13)
    - 1969, 4 folders (Box 13)
    - 1970, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - 1970 (Box 13)
    - 1970 Feb.-Mar. (Box 13)
    - 1971 (Box 13)
    - 1971 Mar.-Oct. (Box 13)
    - 1971 Sept.-Nov. (Box 13)
    - 1972 (Box 14)
    - 1972-1993 (Box 14)
    - 1972 Dec.-1973 Jan. (Box 14)
    - 1973 (Box 14)
    - 1973-1991 (Box 14)
    - 1977 June-1981 Aug. (Box 14)
    - 1977 Apr.-1984 Aug. (Box 14)
    - 1980 Mar.-Aug. (Box 14)
    - 1992 Jan.-1995 Sept. (Box 14)
    - 1994 June (Box 14)
    - 1997-1999 (Box 14)
    - Redstockings meeting notes, 1999 Oct.-2000 Mar. (Box 14)
    - 1999-2002 (Box 15)
    - 2001 Oct. (Box 15)
    - Journals, undated, 6 folders (Box 15)